No, no. You're right.
Someone needs to come talk to him.
(Leonard:)Don't worry, I'll take care of it. Yeah.
All right.
(Leonard:)New plan.
(Leonard:)Howard, you and Raj go to Texas,
I'll stay with Penny in her apartment.
(Penny:)-You're not gonna go with them?
-Well, you know...
(Leonard:)...I gave you the snowflake,
and we were kissing, and--
Come on. I don't wanna go to Texas.
(Howard:)Oh, right. And I do? My people already
crossed the desert once. We're done.
Trust me, you'll be fine. See you.
(Penny:)Well, wait a second, Leonard.
Come on. How can you not go?
(Penny:)-He's your best friend.
-But I already saw him naked.
(Leonard:)-Just come here.
PENNY: No.
(Penny:)I promise I will be here
when you get back.
(Penny:)Just go help Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)-Really?
-Yeah.
(Penny:)We waited a few months.
We can wait a few more days.
(Leonard:)Maybe you can.
(Scene:)Go.